const questions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What's is Nine Tail's name?",
        options: [
            "Gyuuki",
            "Kurama",
            "Choumei",
            "Kyuubi"
        ],
        answer: "Kurama"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "How was Obito/Madara's ultimate plan called?",
        options: [
            "Tsuki no Sekai",
            "Tsuki no Keikaku",
            "Tsuki no Me Keikaku",
            "Infinite Tsukuyomi"
        ],
        answer: 'Tsuki no Me Keikaku'
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "What is the name of Zabuza's sword?",
        options: [
            "Kubikiribocho",
            "Samehada",
            "Kabutowari",
            "Hakarihada"
        ],
        answer: 'Kubikiribocho'
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "How many times did Naruto fail the graduation test from Academy?",
        options: [
            "Once",
            "Four times",
            "Twice",
            "Three times"
        ],
        answer: "Three times"
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "What is the name given to the leader of the Water Village (Kirigakure)?",
        options: [
            "Raikage",
            "Hoshikage",
            "Tsuchikage",
            "Mizukage"
        ],
        answer: "Mizukage"
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "Who of these below has Kekkei Tōta?",
        options: [
            "Hiruzen",
            "Madara",
            "Ōnoki",
            "Kakashi"
        ],
        answer: "Ōnoki"
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "Who was the main Character in Jiraiya's first book — The Tale of the Utterly Gutsy Shinobi?",
        options: [
            "Naruto", 
            "Nagato",
            "Minato",
            "Yahiko"
        ],
        answer: "Naruto"
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "How was Kakashi's father called?",
        options: [
            "White Dog",
            "White Fang",
            "White Lion",
            "White Bird"
        ],
        answer: "White Fang"
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "Who told Naruto he could graduate if he stole the Forbidden Scroll?",
        options: [
            "Kakashi",
            "Iruka",
            "Orochimaru",
            "Mizuki"
        ],
        answer: "Mizuki"
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "What is the name of Itachi's first partner at Akatsuki?",
        options: [
            "Jūzō Biwa",
            "Kisame Hoshikage",
            "Orochimaru",
            "Deidara"
        ],
        answer: 'Jūzō Biwa'
    }
]